kara
Well, it's started, Upokami. This time with Reine Ichioka of Beyonce Subway,
and Momo Kitahara of Ocha-no-Uma.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
First of all, I would like to go behind the scenes with the two MCs.
I, Ichioka, released a single in April,
I, Ichioka, released a single in April, and we had a lot of release events at that time,
There was a day when I performed a song called "Waiting at JR Umeda Station.
I have four songs about the subway,
I have a dialogue part in each of them,
I have to do a lot of talking,
There is a part where I have to explain the stations in the Umeda area,
There is a part where I have to explain the stations in the Umeda area, but on that day, for the first time, I couldn't speak,
I usually think of myself when I say my lines, but I don't think of myself when I say my lines.
I usually say my lines without thinking too much,
But on that day, it had been a while since I had performed,
I practiced a lot in the dressing room, which was unusual for me.
I see.
So I regret that I was too enthusiastic to say what I wanted to say,
So I thought, "I want to continue to take it easy and do things as usual.
I, Kitahara, have recently been involved in Ochanoma's fan club events,
I, Kitahara, have recently been at Ochanoma's fan club events and on Ochanoma's second tour,
I am very happy that I am gradually being allowed to speak out,
I am very happy to hear them call me by my name.
I've been wondering what to call myself at that time,
I was wondering what I should call her, Momo, Momochan, or Momo,
I was wondering what I should call her,
While I was wondering about it, I was OK with the idea of voicing it,
I was left wondering about it for a long time.
I see.
I had asked on my blog what name would be easiest to call you,
Many people said that Momo-chan was the easiest name to call, so I decided on Momo-chan,
So you decided on Momo-chan.
Yay!
We decided on Momo-chan,
I've always wanted to know how you are called,
I've always wanted to know how Ichioka is called, and the number one answer I got was "Icchan,
I heard that "ichan" is easy to call me,
I think you said that Ichioka-san is called Icchan,
Yes, that's right.
So we are all called "ちゃん" together,
That's nice. I like the name Momochan and Icchan. I'm looking forward to working with you.
Let's start with a video of Morning Musume。 23 new member lesson video.
Continuing from last time, we will show you the lesson of two new members of Morning Musume。 23 new members' lesson.
Morning Musume。 17
Passed the exam!
Congratulations!
Morning Musume。.' has been decided to join as the 17th term member.
You have been accepted!
Congratulations!
We are pleased to announce that Morning Musume。 We are pleased to announce that you have been accepted as a member of the 17th term.
Look forward to more and better videos!
I want you to stand with both feet wide, put your hands next to your ears and do the billabillabillabillabillabillar.
1234 like I just did, right back left front right, but I didn't want to do it like this, so I did it straight up.
12345678, 12345678, 12345678, 12345678, 12345678, 12345678, 12345678, 12345678, 12345678...
but now I've got a great one and I'm trying to make it straight by moving my sides and going backwards and stepping on my feet and keeping my shoulders straight.
seven eight seven yes 12345678
7 7 8 7 yes 12345678
There's one more, but it's the last 3c.
567 remember your own timing.
When you're doing ballet, your posture is always in front of you like this, so you have to make your body round, so you have to keep everything straight.
You're going to stay really straight, so...
One, two, three, round.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
I want to input that shape in my mind.
It's probably just a habit.
When do I start?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, step here, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, open, start, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Thank you for watching.
I won't let anyone find out. The truth won't.
Chan chan, chan chan. Five, six, seven, eight.
Until the glittering lilacs. Absolutely from your own eyes.
Never look away from yourself in the mirror
Here... I made a mistake... where did I go wrong?
I'm so embarrassed I made a mistake.
You're going to keep going until the end, eight, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Until the cut comes.
Thank you for watching.
No one will notice. No one can trust you.
You know, every single person has their own dance moves.
You know the part where three, three, three, three, three, three...
I think that part is a little bit more...
It's a little bit more like a frustrated person's dance.
It's the dance of someone who's a little frustrated.
I think.
I want to be frustrated
like I'm trying to shake things off.
Now...
This is just a choreographed dance.
Try to express the feeling of being a little frustrated.
That's what all these songs are about.
One, two, three, four.
I want to follow your fingers all the way down.
And then bring it back.
1,2,3,4
One from here.
Se-no.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la...
Far end of fingerFar end of the finger
Not so much looking at the finger, as looking at the tip of the finger
With the finger
Take your finger out and look at it again
Cue.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then your eyeballs move.
Cue.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you for watching.
Was it a good show? How was it?
It was very confusing.
It was mind-boggling.
I mean, it's the first time, so I'm sure there's a lot of information.
But if you become a member, you're going to get 500 times more information than this.
I'm going to get 500 times more information at once.
I'm trying to get used to it so that I can be prepared for it.
The most important thing is to be able to do what you are told on the same day.
For example, you can write down what you were told today on a piece of paper.
Or you can write down what you couldn't do, or what you felt frustrated about not being able to do.
I want you to write it down so that you can do it and remember it.
I would like you to prepare yourself in such a way that you will be able to do it and remember it.
Let's work hard to become even better at what we do.
Don't be depressed all the time.
That's all I'm going to say.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Choo-choo!
Face is so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny, so tiny. be still, be still, be still, be still, be still, be still be a little bit of a jerk! Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja, Ja
See ja, ja, ja, ja! Yes!
And listen to the sound a little better.
There's all those dancers in there.
Jaja-jaja-jaja-jaja-jaja-jaja-jaja-jaja-jaja-jaja...
Zuka! Zuka! Zuka!
Not here like last year, but last year! Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Do it, do it, do it, do it!
Only feet here.
It would be nice if you could decide where you want to fit in those sounds.
Let's try the B melody again!
Ready?
Doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo...
Shoo!
Now we just need to do it with a little more confidence.
And also, we should be a little more confident, and we should be a little more like, "Hey, we're fighting.
It's like we're fighting.
Thank you for listening.
I'm not gonna let anyone notice.
No. Emotions.
I'm alone
I'm not afraid of anything.
I'm still going to spend time with someone.
I'm not gonna do something so innocent anymore.
I'm just kidding around. I don't care.
I'm turning in for the night.
That's not what you're really doing.
You're running away.
Like last year.
Based on who's home.
I want to.
But that doesn't make this part of me
It's not a lie.
I'm dancing around it
One thing in my easy solution
No one can solve it
Not even you, that Shinwei
I can't do it now
Even if it's love
I was out of rhythm or something.
But I think I got the intro part right.
I think I got it right.
I really don't have time to be
I realized once again that I don't have time to be depressed
I realized that I don't have time to be
I'm still going to do my best
I will do my best for the rest of the lessons.
Compared to the last lesson
I think I got out of my ballet habit a little bit
I think I was able to dance coolly.
I've seen the BPR, and I'm a member of Morning Musume。 I had auditioned for Sakura Oda, who was in the 11th term of Morning Musume,
This summer will be 11 years ago.
Is that right?
I was watching the video of the two auditioning, and it reminded me of my own audition,
I was so nervous, not only about the dance, but also about the people I didn't know and the children who were in the same standing circle as me.
As my dance teacher said earlier, "Be confident,
I was very nervous. As my dance teacher said earlier, "Be confident," but I didn't really know how to be confident,
I remember my dance teacher at the time asking me, "Where are you going? I remember my dance teacher at the time asking me where I was going,
There were about 6 of us. There were about six of us, and we were asked to learn one song in one day,
We all tried our best to learn it together, but one of us had to move to a different place,
I had quite a few memories like that,
I had such memories, but I was wondering what kind of evolution will take place when we perform together with the current members and how our performance will evolve,
I am looking forward to seeing how they will evolve and grow when they perform with the current members.
I, Kitahara, and everyone who took part in the audition for Morning Musume。 19 Love audition,
I saw the video of the lesson and thought that Haruka Inoue and Kataako Inoue were both working very hard,
When the dance sound was played, I saw them naturally keeping the rhythm with their feet,
When the dance sound was played, I could see that they were naturally keeping the rhythm with their feet, and their dance kisses were also getting better.
Please do your best.
That's all for now. 23 new member lesson video.
Angulum Ai no Kedamono June 14 onsize
Let's work hard tomorrow!Good luck tomorrow!
Next is Beyonce's recording for brass instruments for "Yume to Dorenai Yozora ni Shiranai Yozora ni" (I Can't Even Draw a Dream).
Here is the recording of brass instruments for Beyonce's latest single, "Can't Even Dream a Night Sky".
Can you please start from the beginning?
Then, please start from the beginning.
When you expose it then, will you be born as you are?
I'm thinking of the intro 2 movement called "pappappa-pappa",
I want to add a little more nuance than just the exact same staccato.
I wanted to make the third beat of the first measure and the first note of the second measure a little longer staccato.
The third beat of the first bar and the first note of the second bar are a little longer staccato.
I'd say it's a long staccato, and it's got a sequential sound to it.
Yes, it was, yes, I would like the image of pappa-pappa, pappa-pappa, pappa-pappa, pappa-pappa.
Okay.
Okay, let's start with 1C.
Let me go.
It's looking good.
Nice.
It's good.
Yes.
Hey.
Thank you very much.
We will do 5, 6, 7, and 8 of the 3A dash create.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
I will do one rust.
Okay.
I'll do one rust.
It's two before Rasabi. Thank you very much.
114, 115,
I can create the most momentum in this song,
In terms of power,
I mean, in terms of power, or in terms of the sense of excitement,
Is there a higher level?
I think so.
Are you sure?
Can I ask you to give it a try?
Yes.
♪ BGM
Up to the 200th 110, please.
To the 200th, yes.
♪ BGM
That's good.
I'll just do 108.
123?
From this point on, it's more like a big band, so it's okay if we all play a little differently, rather than all together tightly.
I think it would be good if you could make it naturally in a cool direction from the point of view of the players and the characteristics of the instruments.
I thought it would be good if you could make it in a natural way.
It's big.
Yes.
It's a little detailed, but is it like a 117th note?
Thank you very much.
Okay, we'll go to the next one.
Let's hear it from Matt until the end.
Okay.
Gold this time.
Thank you very much.
Gold award and overall.
It's already a great cut. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
My name is Yusuke Kato, and I was in charge of arranging the music for this project.
I already had a certain concept in mind when Mr. Hoshibe gave me the demo and materials for the music.
We decided to use a brass band as the theme this time.
So we had that concept in mind as well.
I wanted to make it more like a brass band, whether you have real brass band experience or not.
I tried to make each note sound like a brass band arrangement, whether you have real brass band experience or not.
My job was to create the individual sounds and put the arrangement together.
That's right.
If you follow the score exactly and ask everyone to play like this
I often get the impression that I'm good at it.
It gives the impression that you are good at what you do.
But if you listen to the music, you'll be able to enjoy it.
If you want the audience to enjoy the music, you have to make it enjoyable for them.
the performers who are playing must also enjoy playing, and of course, the same goes for the singers.
And of course, the same goes for the singers.
I don't want to forget that aspect of the music.
I tried to keep that in mind when recording this song.
I tried to be careful in this recording.
Beyond's songs are also written by other artists
but this time, too, I put a lot of thought into the instruments and
but this time, too, I put a lot of thought into the instruments
and the tempo of the song.
I put a lot of attention to details.
I've tried to be as particular as possible, so that it's okay to put too much into it.
I've put a lot of attention to detail into this album, so I hope you'll take the time to listen to it.
I think you'll discover a lot of things if you listen to it carefully.
I'm sure you'll discover a lot.
I hope you will listen to it
I hope you will enjoy it after listening to it.
I would like to ask you to listen to the music after you have listened to it once.
I hope you can feel how I played the instruments and how I felt.
I think it was taken in such a way that the audience can understand how the instruments sounded and how I felt when I played them.
I would be very happy if you could listen to it over and over again.
The song "Dancing in the night sky where I can't even draw a dream"...The song "Dancing in the night sky where I can't even draw a dream" is inspired by a chorus and a brass band.
It is based on the motif of chorus and brass band.
Even the members of the band actually harmonized during the song.
There are parts that are a bit like a chorus part.
It's a song that you can enjoy to the fullest, intertwined with the instruments you've just seen.
It's a song that you can enjoy to the fullest.
It's not often that we get to see a recording of these instruments, but I'm sure you'll be able to enjoy the music to the fullest.
Both the relector and the performers are professionals.
I was able to learn a lot of details from the professionals.
I was impressed by the way they immediately put things into practice after just a little explanation.
I thought it was amazing.
Beyonce had the opportunity to perform with the orchestra.
Beyonce has had the opportunity to perform with orchestras and has had more contact with the instruments.
I hope that we can convey the quality of the songs more firmly.
I felt a sense of mission to sing and dance in order to convey the quality of the songs more clearly.
I felt a greater sense of mission.
After watching the video of the recording, we were able to learn more about the music.
I love the songs, but
I love the song, but I want to perform it with more love each and every time.
I, Ikutahara, love this song very much.
I love the grandeur and sparkle of this song.
I love the members' singing, of course, but I also love the brass instruments and the way they play it.
the brass instruments and so on.
I was very happy to know something new about this song.
I'm very happy to know something new.
I was very happy to know something new, and I discovered something new.
That's all for now, Beyonce, on the night sky where you can't even draw a dream, it's a brass recording.
Be sure to watch to the end!
Beyonce, Ichioka Reina from the subway, and Momo Kitahara from the tea house, up Kami.
Here is the next one.
Tsubaki Factory Skip Skip Skip Vocal Recording
Watch the vocal recording of Skip Skip Skip and Kisora Minuma from Tsubaki Factory's latest single.
Okay, let's start filming.
I'll start with the A melody of the first verse.
This song is rather groovy.
I don't want to take too many shots.
I'd rather keep it fresh.
I want to get the momentum going.
Let's do it.
Reading out loud.
After this, you're still putting on the accent, but try to make it as strong as possible.
Yes, sir.
And the heart, too.
Also, I'm going to see you today... and it's a crescendo mark. I hope it makes you sound like you're listening to me.
I hope the way you say "we'll see each other" makes it sound like "we'll see each other".
It'd be nice if you could make it sound like that.
B melody
OK, let's go to B-melody.
Even the dust before the wind will dance, I'll jump on the happiness and dance
Meet at the west exit ticket gate I'll hurry up and head there
Let's hurry up and head out
I'll stop at one or two
And you know what? I think I'd better breathe before the happy one.
If you do it after the second one, it'll be a little too busy.
Even the dust before the wind will dance. We must jump and dance to happiness.
Let's try it once with that.
Hmmm...
Even the dust before the wind will dance Jump on your black happiness and dance
West exit turnstiles, last stop, I'll hurry up and get there
Yeah, now it's perfect
OK, let's go to the end
Okay, let's go to the chorus.
I want to make it so the audience can get into the groove.
Yes, sir.
Let's get the singers in the groove, too.
Let's get the singers in the groove.
Okay, take one.
West exit turnstiles, last stop, we're on our way
Skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip.
Skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip.
I don't know this song, but I'm gonna get on it
I'll stand out tonight, my bread
Skip, skip, skip, skip, temptation, temptation, temptation, temptation
I'm gonna get on and off the train Romance, romance, romance
I can't just leave it like this, I can't just leave it like this, I can't just leave it like this
Skip, skip, skip, skip
Nice, just like that.
Romance's a little pitchy right now
Romance.
Yeah, romance.
Skips.
There you go.
Settle in there, please.
And skip, skip, skip to the end.
It's kind of hard to say.
Skip, skip, skip, skip, skip.
Don't be too skippy-skippy. Skipp, skipp, skipp, skipp, skipp.
Skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip
Because that turn is skippy-skippy.
A little difference.
I'd like to be able to tell the difference.
Okay, one more time.
West Exit turnstiles. Gather around. We're on our way.
Skip, skip, skip, skip
It's windy and stylish.
It's more fun when it's fast
I don't know this song, but I'm going to try it
Hello, my parts stand outGood evening, my parts.
totally suki, suki, suki
seduction waku seduction
Ride me, ride me, romance
even my heart beats
it's so hard to leave it alone
We can rock
skip skip skip skip
OK, let's move on to the next three skip-skip-skip at the beginning of the first chorus.
Skip skip skip skip this often!
Tension high.
That's good. Perfect.
Next, let's change the words.
Suki-suki-suki.
We're the same, aren't we?
That's the same, isn't it?
So I'll make a little difference and say "Suki-suki-suki.
Heart.
Please make it "Suki" like "Suki, Suki, heart.
I love it! I love it! I like it!
OK, perfect!
OK, I'm done!
Thank you very much!
I, Kitahara, think this song is very cheerful and uplifting.
I thought Ms. Shinnuma's lovely voice was very well suited for this song, and when I saw the VTR, I couldn't help but dance my heart out!
I think there were instructions to put a heart at the end of the song, and I was amazed at how quickly Ms. Shinnuma responded to those instructions.
I was impressed by the way she sang the song with so many different expressions.
I always think that Kisora Shinnuma's voice goes well with this kind of cheerful music.
I've always thought that Kisora Shinnuma's voice goes well with such bright songs, and I thought that it was used to great effect this time as well.
And when I saw the other members of Tsubaki Factory performing, I was also impressed by the way they sang the songs.
I saw the girls of Tsubaki Factory actually performing the song and they were all smiling.
I was very impressed by the smiles on everyone's faces as they performed this song.
I hope Beyonce will try her hand at this kind of song someday.
That's all for now, this is the vocal recording of Kisora Niinuma of Tsubaki Factory Skipskipskipskips.
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't
I wouldn't kiss you okay
I couldn't even tell you
Pride Bright July 12 on-issue!
Let's work hard tomorrow!
It's time to say goodbye to upcami, the show that Reina Ichioka and Momo Kitahara have been presenting for you.
We've been watching a lot of videos this time, but I, Kitahara, would like to introduce you to two new members of Morning Musume。 23 new members' dance lessons left a strong impression on me.
Seeing them working so hard made me go back to the basics, or rather, I wanted to work harder.
Yes, I, Reina Ichioka, was a brass instrumentalist for the recording of "Can't even dream a dream in the night sky.
I feel very strongly that I was able to perform this song thanks to the help or cooperation of so many people.
I would like to keep performing each and every time with great care.
Up-Kami is a program that goes behind the scenes of the production of the various artists who belong to the Up-Front Group.
We'll introduce you to a lot of things you don't normally get to see, so please subscribe to our channel!
This time up-cam's partners were Reina Ichioka of Beyons Subway and Momo Kitahara of Ochanomama!
Good bye!
Next time on Upokami,
The making of Angulum's "Beast of Love" music video shoot
And,
Beyonce: Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler" recording session.
Enjoy!
Please subscribe to our channel.